

Contact Information

623-200-1577

sawlhung@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sawl-rah

http://www.rahsawl.com

Technical Portfolio

Databases/Cloud

• SQL, Oracale, Excel, , Salesforce Tableau Sap - .NET Frameworks GCloud. AWS Cloud- Microsoft Azure

Marketing Automation and Email Marketing

• Marketo, MailChimp, Bizible GohighLevel Jira, Trello

Code

 PHP HTML Javascript- Python, - API -Powershell - ASP.NET ABAP- JSON-TCPDUMP -NMAP

SEO & SEM

 Google Analytics, Adobe Frameworks, Moz, Adwords, SEM Rush

Core Competencies

- Multitasking & Adaptability
- Teamwork & Leadership
- Project Management
- Critical Thinking
- Problem Solving
- Strategical Planning
- Pressure Situation Handling
- Self-learning & Enthusiastic

SAWLEH ABDURRAHMAN

Senior Business Analyst PM / Software Engineer

PROFILE SUMMARY

Goal-oriented, highly analytical, and accountable Business Analyst, Software Engineer and Business Professional with 8+ years of extensive experience and demonstrated success in driving organizational growth, performance, and overall value, along with the acute business acumen in the following areas of expertise:

| Business Development & Analysis | Strategic Leadership |
|---------------------------------|----------------------|
| Client Relationship Management | Logistic Management |
| Cross Cultural Collaboration | Software Engineering |

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Logistic Management Specialist Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Jan 2020 - Present

- Created in-depth reports and presentations on a business's processes.
- Designed and offered forecasts and expectations while suggesting solutions to business problems.
- Established methods for testing business applications and creating templates for reports used to monitor application effectiveness.
- Orchestrated workshops and staff presentations within a company.
- Operated closely with key customers to keep them updated on process changes designed to improve service.

Client Relationship Specialist

Vanguard

Mar 2019 - Jan 2020

- Operated as a Client Relationship Specialist for almost one year.
- Evaluated client profiles to understand and recommend new product offerings to increase revenue flow

Founder

LCN Ummati LLC

Jun 2016- Jun 2019

- Started my own consulting company, developed and maintained a company's vision, mission statement, and strategic plan.
- Identified new opportunities for revenue growth, including new products or services that meet unmet needs in the marketplace.
- Spearheaded startup consultation process and operated as the IT Recruitment Specialists.
- Researched and implemented new potential trends within the industry.
- Discovered new opportunities and markets for businesses to expand.
- Discovered new financial avenues to keep a company solvent.
- As founder and Project manager, I was hands-on diving into coding projects and underwriting languages and formats helping companies integrate client-server services and managing operations efficiently.
- Overviewed remote and on-site teams building mobile and web applications.

Certifications & Trainings

Google IT Automation Professional

Google & Coursera

Salesforce Certified Administrator (SCA)

Salesforce & Udemy

Google IT Support Specialization

Google IT Support & Coursera

Technical Support Fundamentals

Google & Coursera

Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking

Google & Coursera

System Administration and IT Infrastructure Services

Google & Coursera

IT Security: Defense against the Digital

Dark Arts

Google & Coursera

Operating Systems and You: Becoming a

Power User

Google & Coursera

Personal Interests

Causes

- Fitness & Sports
- Volunteer work
- Fashion
- Music
- Playing Chess
- Hiking

<u>Causes</u>

- Economic Empowerment
- Education
- Environment
- Human Rights
- Poverty Alleviation
- Social Services
- Science and Technology

- Navigated as a Diligent founding support specialist and gained 3 years of experience and company contracted for a large cloud services agency.
- Acted as the Consultant on advisory panel of Buyers Management team.

Acting Consultant / Dealer

Maui Teeth Whitening

Jun 2015 - May 2016

- Operated a Maui whitening franchise and sold it.
- Worked as the acting Consultant on board advisory panel of buyers management team.

Reference: Leigh Tomayo (623)-419-2053

Business Clerk

Haynes Furniture

Jan 2015 – Jun 2015

- Worked for Haynes Furniture as a business clerk for their outlet 'The Dump'.
- Offered and provided customer service, type orders, dealt with warranty issues and applied for finance and much more.

Reference: Kim Jaggers kjaggers@thedump.com (602)-872-6090

Store Operator

T.J Enterprises (Chevron)

Feb 2013 – Jan 2015

- Worked as an employee at TJ enterprise's store Chevron for two years.
- Ontained handsome experience in dealing with customers and maintaining a healthy working environment.
- I was invoicing merchandise and restocking items while working here. Reference: Hem Lata (480)-232-3463

Store Operator

Pazeb Boutique & Coffee

Jan 2013 – May 2015

- Worked for Pazeb's Boutique and coffee shop as a summer job
- This job improved my communication skills and ability to handle food items.

Reference: AJ Ryan (480)-719-9226 Reference: Farah Ramon (480-522-4128 Reference: Sami Kediy (480-347-7814

ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE

Master's Degree in Computer and Information Systems Security/Information Assurance 2021 - 2024

Assurance Arizona State University

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2017 - 2019

Arizona State University

Bachelor of Business Administration

2015 - 2018

Arizona State University

Associate of Arts and Sciences - AAS, Computer / Information Technology Administration and Management 2014 - 2016

Penn Foster

• Grade - 4.00